<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><!--
  ~
  ~ @brief Copyright (c) 2023 Gabriel Marquette
  ~
  ~ Copyright (c) 2023 Gabriel Marquette. All rights reserved.
  ~
  -->

<resources>
    <string name="play">Play</string>
    <string name="hard">Hard</string>
    <string name="logo_app">Logo</string>
    <string name="easy">Easy</string>
    <string name="guess_1">Guess 1</string>
    <string name="guess_2">Guess 2</string>
    <string name="guess_3">Guess 3</string>
    <string name="guess_4">Guess 4</string>
    <string name="guess_5">Guess 5</string>
    <string name="guess_6">Guess 6</string>
    <string name="make_your_guess">Make your guess</string>
    <string name="yes">Yes</string>
    <string name="no">No</string>
    <string name="do_you_want_to_play_again">Do you want to play again ?</string>
    <string name="the_answer_was">"The answer was : "</string>
    <string name="default_difficulty">EASY</string>
    <string name="difficulty">"Difficulty : "</string>
    <string name="age">Age :</string>
    <string name="type">Type :</string>
    <string name="prime">Bounty :</string>
    <string name="chapitre">Chapter :</string>
    <string name="fruit">Devil Fruit :</string>
    <string name="statut">Status :</string>
    <string name="equipage">Crew :</string>
    <string name="niveau">Level :</string>
    <string name="import_datas">Import Datas</string>
    <string name="wins">Wins :</string>
    <string name="loses">Loses :</string>
    <string name="last_update">Last Update :</string>
    <string name="fruitHelp">"These images can be used to determine whether or not the character in question possesses a fruit. If they don't, it's the fruit with the red cross; if they've eaten a demon fruit, it's the classic demon fruit image. "</string>
    <string name="bountyHelp">This circle is used to determine the character\'s bonus. The bounty will be determined in relation to that of the chosen character. The bounty of the given character will be displayed, along with an indication of the character to be found. There are several types of bounty: those with Md are expressed in billions of berrys, those with Mi in millions of berrys, otherwise in berrys. Those that are unknown are displayed as Unknown, and citizens and marines have bonuses equivalent to 0. Example: Character to be found Monkey D. Luffy: 3 Md, Character chosen: Tony-Tony Chopper: 500. In this case, the image will show 500, compared with Tony-Tony Chopper\'s bounty, and an upward arrow to indicate that the bounty sought is higher.</string>
    <string name="ChapterHelp">Le troisième cercle est le chapitre où le personnage est apparu pour la première fois. De la même façon que pour la prime, le chapitre est accompagné d\'une flèche permettant de savoir si ce dernier est apparu avant ou après le personnage recherché.</string>
    <string name="TypeHelp">This circle determines the character\'s type, of which there are 4:      - Pirate: represented by the straw hat crew symbol. It represents all the spirates and brigands of the One Piece world.      - Marine: Represented by the navy symbol. The navy symbol is used for navy characters, celestial dragons, characters linked to the Impel Down underwater prison and the World Government.      - Revolutionary: Represented by the revolutionary army symbol. It represents all members of the revolutionary army.      - Citizen: Represented by the symbol on the One Piece logo. It represents all citizens of the One Piece world.</string>
    <string name="AliveHelp">"These images show whether the character is currently alive or not. The first image shows when the character is alive, and the other when he's dead.  "</string>
    <string name="AgeHelp">This circle represents the character\'s age. In the same way as for the appearance chapter, arrows indicate whether or not the character is older than the one chosen</string>
    <string name="CrewHelp">"These images represent the different crews. The first image shows the crew of straw-hatted pirates. The second is the pirates without a full crew. The last is the citizens. For the navy, the World Government, Impel Down, has its own crew and therefore its own logo. "</string>
    <string name="WRHelp">"These circles determine whether the answer is correct in relation to the character you're looking for. If the circle is green, then the character you're looking for has the same characteristics as the character you've chosen.      Example: Roronoa Zoro: No demon fruit, Vinsmoke Sanji: No demon fruit. In this case, if the character you're looking for is Roronoa Zoro, then the Demon Fruit characteristic will be green, as both characters haven't eaten any. "</string>
</resources>